Igor Pavlenko

Prague, Tel: (+420) 773 088 415

Czech Rep**ublic** Email : igor_pavlenko@msn.com

Website: www.igorpavlenko.com
GitHub: https://github.com/lgor2122
linkedin.com/in/igor-pavlenko2122

Objective:

I'm a passionate Full Stack developer with over 1 year experience working with React, Laravel and Wordpress platform. I enjoy coding and solving puzzles. I have an extensive work experience in multinational working environment I really enjoy meeting new people and discover their culture.

I am in Prague at the moment finishing my Full Stack Web Development course in Bootcamp Praha, will be available for career opportunities in April.

Education:

Jan. 2019 – March 2019 – degree in progress

Coding Bootcamp Praha – Full Stack Web Development

April 2017 - Current – "Team Tree House"

https://teamtreehouse.com/igorpavlenko

Sep. 2003 – March 2007 – Bachelor's degree

EUFIMB Kiev, Ukraine – Business Management

Degree in: "People Management and Organizational Development"

IT SKILLS:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL, React, Laravel, jQuery,

Programming Bootstrap, Ajax, JSON, REST Services, Web API, GULP, MS Visual

Studio, Git MAMP

Languages Spoken: English, Ukrainian, Russian

EXPERIENCE:

February 2018 – (Around 1 year)

Manama, Bahrain

Freelance Software Developer http://www.igdevelopers.com/

- Developing modern and responsive websites and web applications on multiple platforms:
 CMS, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, LARAVEL
- Consulting clients to outline website goals, illustrate wire frame, and site functionality, training staff on web application functionality
- Creating Web pages and applications as per the customers requirements
- Managing websites content updates, debugging

Aug 2014 - Dec 2018 (4 years 4 months)

Manama, Bahrain

Volvo Passenger - Sales Supervisor

- Create Sales campaigns mostly through digital channels
- Manage Volvo Bahrain Social media accounts
- Managing Sales Team to achieve monthly/annual sales target objectives

My main accomplishment on this role was getting promoted to Supervisor position overseen team of salespeople. During that period I have increased the annual sales revenue by almost 70%, I managed that with Volvo introducing a new models and we were able to capitalize on that opportunity.

Sep. 2012 - June 2014 ()

Manama, Bahrain

Tag Heuer Boutique - Store in Charge

Attending customers and other sales related activities

Nov. 2009 – Aug 2013

Chicago, III

Ford Passenger – Sales Executive

Attending customers and other sales related activities